and those of you Tepper students in the back will be very interested in this. So we found that the passwords created by people affiliated with the school of computer science were actually 1.8 times stronger than those affiliated with the business school. We have lots of other really interesting demographic information as well. The other interesting thing that we found is that when we compared the Carnegie Mellon passwords to the Mechanical Turk-generated passwords, there was actually a lot of similarities, and so this helped validate our research method and show that actually, collecting passwords using these Mechanical Turk studies is actually a valid way to study passwords. So that was good news. Okay, I want to close by talking about some insights I gained while on sabbatical last year in the Carnegie Mellon art school. One of the things that I did is I made a number of quilts, and I made this quilt here. It's called "Security Blanket." (Laughter) And this quilt has the 1,000 most frequent passwords stolen from the RockYou website. And the size of the passwords is proportional to how frequently they appeared in the stolen dataset. And what I did is I created this word cloud, and I went through all 1,000 words, and I categorized them into loose thematic categories. And it was, in some cases, it was kind of difficult to figure out what category they should be in, and then I color-coded them. So here are some examples of the difficulty. So "justin." Is that the name of the user, their boyfriend, their son? Maybe they're a Justin Bieber fan. Or "princess." Is that a nickname? Are they Disney princess fans? Or maybe that's the name of their cat. "Iloveyou" appears many times in many different languages. There's a lot of love in these passwords. If you look carefully, you'll see there's also some profanity, but it was really interesting to me to see that there's a lot more love than hate in these passwords. And there are animals, a lot of animals, and "monkey" is the most common animal and the 14th most popular password overall. And this was really curious to me, and I wondered, "Why are monkeys so popular?" And so in our last password study, any time we detected somebody creating a password with the word "monkey" in it, we asked them why they had a monkey in their password. And what we found out -- we found 17 people so far, I think, who have the word "monkey" -- We found out about a third of them said they have a pet named "monkey" or a friend whose nickname is "monkey," and about a third of them said that they just like monkeys and monkeys are really cute. And that guy is really cute. So it seems that at the end of the day, when we make passwords, we either make something that's really easy to type, a common pattern, or things that remind us of the word password or the account that we've created the password for, or whatever. Or we think about things that make us happy, and we create our password based on things that make us happy. And while this makes typing and remembering your password more fun, it also makes it a lot easier to guess your password. So I know a lot of these TED Talks are inspirational and they make you think about nice, happy things, but when you're creating your password, try to think about something else. Thank you. (Applause)
y aquellos de Uds. estudiantes de Tepper de atrás estarán muy interesados en esto. Así nos encontramos con que las contraseñas creadas por las personas afiliadas a la escuela de ciencias de la computación en realidad eran 1,8 veces más seguras que las de los afiliados a la escuela de negocios. Tenemos también información demográfica muy interesante. Otra cosa interesante que encontramos es que al comparar las contraseñas de Carnegie Mellon con las contraseñas generadas por Mechanical Turk, había una gran cantidad de similitudes, y así que esto ayudó a validar nuestro método de investigación y mostrar que en realidad, la recogida de contraseñas utilizando estos estudios de Mechanical Turk es en realidad una forma válida para estudiar las contraseñas. Así que fue una buena noticia. Bien, quiero cerrar hablando de algunas ideas que tuve durante mi año sabático el año pasado en la escuela de arte de Carnegie Mellon. Una de las cosas que hice es una serie de edredones, y he hecho este edredón de aquí. Se llama "Manta de Seguridad". (Risas) Este edredón tiene las 1000 contraseñas robadas con más frecuencia del sitio web RockYou. El tamaño de las contraseñas es proporcional a la frecuencia con que aparecían en el conjunto de datos robados. Lo que hice es crear esta nube de palabras, y examiné todas las 1000 palabras, y las categoricé en categorías temáticas sueltas. Y, en algunos casos, era un poco difícil de entender en qué categoría debían estar y entonces las identifiqué por colores. Así que estos son algunos ejemplos de la dificultad. Digamos "justin". ¿Es ese el nombre del usuario, su novio, su hijo? Tal vez son un fan de Justin Bieber. O "princesa". ¿Es un apodo? ¿Son fans de las princesas de Disney? O tal vez ese es el nombre de su gato. "Iloveyou" aparece muchas veces en muchos idiomas diferentes. Hay mucho amor en estas contraseñas. Si miran atentamente, verán que hay también algunas palabras soeces, pero lo que fue realmente interesante ver para mí es que hay mucho más amor que odio en estas contraseñas. Y hay animales, una gran cantidad de animales, y "mono" es el animal más común y la 14 contraseña más popular. Y esto fue realmente curioso para mí, y me pregunté: "¿Por qué son tan populares los monos?" Y así, en nuestro último estudio sobre contraseñas, cuando detectamos que alguien crea una contraseña usando "mono", les preguntamos por qué tenían un mono en su contraseña. Y lo que averiguamos... encontramos 17 personas hasta el momento que tienen la palabra "mono"... Encontramos que un tercio de ellos dijo que tienen una mascota llamada "mono" o un amigo cuyo apodo es "mono" y alrededor de un tercio de ellos dijo simplemente que le gustan los monos y que los monos son muy lindos. Y ese joven es muy lindo. Así, parece que al final, cuando hacemos las contraseñas, hacemos algo que o es muy fácil de escribir, un patrón común, o cosas que nos recuerdan a la palabra contraseña o a la cuenta para la que hemos creado la contraseña, o lo que sea. O pensamos acerca de las cosas que nos hacen felices, y creamos nuestra contraseña basados en las cosas que nos hacen felices. Y si bien esto facilita la escritura y recordarla es más divertido, también hace que sea mucho más fácil descifrar la contraseña. Así que sé que un montón de estas charlas TED son fuente de inspiración y hacen pensar sobre cosas agradables y felices, pero cuando estén creando su contraseña, traten de pensar en otra cosa. Gracias. (Aplausos)